你干嘛  你要改吗
What are you doing? Are you correcting it?
所有格的  "的"
Apostrophe "S".
我们要和法西斯主义作斗争  不是标点符号
We're fighting against fascism, not punctuation.
带上帽子  穿上学士服
Wow. Dig the cap and gownship.
好像回到学校一样
I feel like I'm back in school, man.
你应该回炉重造
You should be back in school.
这文章看起来像一群豺狼写的
This looks like it was written by a pack of jackals.
听着亚伯  你变得有些讨人厌
You know what, Abe? You're becoming a bit of a drag.
讨厌  讨厌  讨厌鬼
Drag, drag, drag.
我们才完成首刊诶
We just finished our first paper.
对啊
That's right.
埃兹拉实现了自我突破
And Ezra has outdone himself.
我以为你是艾伦的女朋友
I thought you were Alan's girlfriend.
女人不是任何男人的所有物
No woman is any man's property.
你应该关注内容
You should be looking at the ideas.
不是拼写和语法
Not the spelling. Not the grammar.